Susan Krause

VP Marketing & Client Relations, Manley Films & Media

Summary

15+ years marketing communications and public relations

10 + years copywriting for web and business communications

7+ years magazine writing/editing

Specialties: Project management, content marketing, blogging, content development, public affairs & public communications, marketing planning.

Passion Projects: Special education, gifted education, STEAM, middle grade and YA Fiction.

Experience

VP Marketing & Client Relations at Manley Films & Media

May 2015 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Develop and implement client retention strategies to ensure that we make clients our biggest fans.

Primary contact and lead client touch point for the day to day care and service of all MF&M clients.

Spearhead customer service strategies and improvements and upgrades

Write high profile proposals

Participate in regular planning sessions with both clients and prospects. Assisting the sales effort by setting the standard of high quality of care and service a client will receive.

Marketing/promotion for Manley Films & Media

Sr. Marketing Manager at Guardian 8 Corporation

October 2013 - April 2015 (1 year 7 months)

Responsible for all marketing related activities including advertising, events, PR, writing, B2B, strategy, planning and all marketing materials.

Director of Communications at Vertigent, a Division of Earth911, Inc.

June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

Marketing, public relations and communications for Earth911, Inc. and its client solutions division, Vertigent.

Director of Communications at Earth911, Inc.

May 2011 - August 2013 (2 years 4 months)

Earth911, Inc. supports the growth and goals of businesses and the information needs of consumers on topics relevant to recycling and low-waste through Earth911 Media and Vertigent.

Director of Campus Marketing and PR at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University Prescott

January 2009 - May 2011 (2 years 5 months)

Support enrollment management in meeting strategic goals for recruiting new students.

Communications at City of Prescott

2001 - 2006 (5 years)

Projects

Vertigent Overview Video

May 2013 to June 2013

Members: Susan Krause, Alana Sabin

Vertigent provides a simple, local and accurate way to communicate with consumers about proper disposal of goods.

Skills & Expertise

Business Writing and Communications

Web Content Management

Creative Strategy

Public Communications

Project Management

Marketing

Social Media

Marketing Communications

Social Media Marketing

Public Relations

Blogging

Editing

Copywriting

Press Releases

Newsletters

Content Management

Strategic Planning

Marketing Strategy

Online Advertising

Sustainability

Non-profits

Social Networking

Strategic Communications

Media Relations

Communication

Business Writing

Corporate Social Responsibility

Nonprofits

Brand Development

Advertising

Corporate Communications

Creative Direction

Copy Editing

Email Marketing

Journalism

Facebook

Publications

Magazines

Public Speaking

Content Development

Internal Communications

Editorial

Web Content

Online Marketing

New Media

Publishing

SEO

Creative Writing

Content Strategy

Feature Articles

Education

Utah State University

BS, American Studies, 1988 - 1990

WHS

Interests

Special education advocacy, gifted education, ADHD, kid lit, STEM education

Susan Krause

VP Marketing & Client Relations, Manley Films & Media



2 people have recommended Susan

"Susan is a marketing genius! From writing copy to final production, Susan knows how to position the product to the end user in a way that is best for them to hear. I worked with Susan at Guardian 8 Corporation and found her work to be creative, timely and on target."

— **Judy Dixon**, *Sales Director Atlantic Region*, *Guardian 8 Corporation*, worked with Susan at Guardian 8 Corporation

"Susan is the best period!"

— scott dodgson, reported to Susan at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University Prescott

Contact Susan on LinkedIn